Previously on the show. Slowy fell sick.
Ở tập trước, Cừu Chậm Chạp bị ốm.
The stars initially thought that Wolffy and the goats made him sick.
Các vì sao nghĩ Sói Xám và các bạn cừu làm ông ấy ốm.
The goats insisted on helping, which finally got Slowy better.
Các bạn cừu đã giúp Cừu Chậm Chạp đỡ hơn.
The stars have also come to accept Wolffy and the goats.
Các vì sao đã chấp nhận Sói Xám và các bạn cừu.
But how can they make Slowy go back to the way he used to be?
Nhưng làm sao để họ biến Cừu Chậm Chạp trở lại ban đầu?
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: The Invincible Baby"
"Hòn Đảo Bay: Thám Hiểm Bầu Trời: Bé Con Bất Bại."
So you ate the fruit from the tree and became small?
Ông ăn quả từ cây và trở nên nhỏ hơn?
Those are infantilising fruits.
Đó là quả sơ sinh.
They make people young again.
Chúng khiến mọi người trẻ lại.
Baby, it's time to eat.
Bé con, đến giờ ăn rồi.
I made something delicious for you.
Ta làm đồ ngon cho con.
I can't drink from a milk bottle in front of the children. That's too embarrassing.
Ta không thể uống sữa bình trước mặt lũ trẻ. Quá mất mặt.
Grandpa Elder. The chief is actually an adult, not a baby.
Trưởng Lão. Trưởng Làng là người lớn, không phải em bé.
He became a baby after eating one of those infantilizing fruits.
Ông ấy biến thành em bé sau khi ăn quả sơ sinh.
You keep saying he's an adult. How old is he?
Vậy ông ấy bao nhiêu tuổi?
He's in his 80s.
Ông tầm 80 tuổi.
That's still very young. I'm more than 2,000 years old.
Thế vẫn rất trẻ. Ta đã hơn 2.000 tuổi rồi.
Come, drink some milk.
Hãy uống sữa nào.
How can we turn Chief back to what he used to be?
Sao ta có biến Trưởng Làng trở lại ban đầu?
You can look for Time Star.
Cháu có thể tìm Sao Thời Gian.
Who is that?
Đó là ai ạ?
He's the most famous performance judge in the sky.
Đó là giám khảo nổi tiếng nhất trên bầu trời.
If he gives a performance five stars, everyone will eagerly come to see it.
Nếu ông ta cho màn trình diễn năm sao, mọi người sẽ hào hứng tới xem.
But what does that have to do with Chief?
Vậy thì liên quan gì tới Trưởng Làng ạ?
That's because his superpower is to make people old.
Sức mạnh của ông ta là làm mọi người già đi.
How can we find him?
Vậy tìm ông ta ở đâu ạ?
He's always alone. It's hard to find him.
Ông ta luôn một mình. Rất khó để tìm.
But...
Nhưng...
But what?
Nhưng gì?
If our troupe manages to get 10,000 likes,
Nếu đoàn kịch của ta đạt 10.000 lượt thích
he'll definitely come.
thì ông ta nhất định sẽ tới.
Great! What does he look like?
Tuyệt! Vậy ông ta trông như thế nào?
Um, I think there's a photo of him in Handsome Star's place.
Ta nghĩ có ảnh của ông ta ở chỗ Sao Đẹp Trai.
Who's that? Can he make me handsome?
Đó là ai? Ông ấy có thể làm cháu đẹp trai không?
No.
Không.
That's because his superpower is to make himself handsome when no one's around.
Sức mạnh của ông ấy là làm ông ấy đẹp khi không có ai bên cạnh.
What can I do to those stars so I can catch Slowy?
Ta nên làm gì với những ngôi sao đó để bắt Cừu Chậm Chạp?
Pay.
Trả tiền.
That's too simple.
Thế quá dễ dàng.
I'm asking you to pay now!
Em bảo anh trả tiền!
Okay.
Được rồi.
Go next door and get me some facial masks. I'm going to buy shoes.
Đi mua cho em mặt nạ. Em sẽ đi mua giày.
Okay.
Được.
There are so many people buying masks.
Quá nhiều người mua mặt nạ.
Grandpa.
Ông lão.
Who did you call grandpa?
Ngươi gọi ai ông lão?
Have you ever seen such a fit grandpa?
Thấy ông nào khỏe mạnh như này chưa?
Are you not a grandpa?
Không phải ông lão ư?
Then what are you doing at the senior activity center?
Vậy anh làm gì ở viện dưỡng lão?
What? Senior activity center?
Trung tâm dưỡng lão?
Oh, dear. I came to the wrong place.
Ôi, mình đã đến nhầm chỗ.
Senior activity center?
Viện dưỡng lão?
So old people love senior activity centers.
Thì ra người già thích viện dưỡng lão.
What if I open one?
Nếu như mình mở một nơi?
The stars will be at the center all the time.
Các vì sao sẽ ở luôn luôn trung tâm.
Then I'll have lots of time to get the goats.
Và mình sẽ có nhiều thời gian để bắt lũ cừu.
That's a great idea.
Ý tưởng tuyệt vời.
Where are my masks?
Mặt nạ đâu?
How handsome you are.
Mình thật đẹp trai.
Grandpa Handsome Star.
Ông Sao Đẹp Trai.
Who's that?
Ai đó?
Sorry to disturb you, Grandpa Handsome Star.
Xin lỗi đã làm phiền ông.
We need your help.
Chúng cháu cần ông giúp.
This is the photo of Time Star. Here you go.
Ảnh của Sao Thời Gian đây.
Handsome Star, let's go out and have some fun.
Sao Đẹp Trai, ra ngoài chơi thôi.
The picture of grandpa Time Star flew away.
Ảnh của Sao Đẹp Trai bay mất rồi.
Thank you.
Cảm ơn.
Today is the official opening of Wolffy's senior activity center!
Hôm nay là khai trương viện dưỡng lão của Sói Xám.
Come. Come inside.
Hãy vào đi.
Dear friends,
Các bạn,
this is Wolffy's senior activity center.
đây là viện dưỡng lão của Sói Xám.
Look at the layout.
Hãy nhìn sự bày trí.
Look at the facilities. It's so...
Hãy nhìn các thiết bị. Chúng rất...
Isn't it amazing?
Tuyệt phải không?
It's mediocre.
Cũng thường thôi.
But since you just opened, we'll come to visit.
Vì ngươi đã mở, bọn ta sẽ ghé thăm.
Thank you.
Cảm ơn.
I need to think of a way to get Slowy.
Ta phải tìm cách bắt Cừu Chậm Chạp.
By the way, is the baby still feeling unwell?
Bé con vẫn thấy không khỏe ư?
Shall I give him a check-up?
Tôi có nên kiểm tra bé không?
Well...
Hừm...
We don't want him to get sick again.
Chúng ta không muốn bé lại bị ốm.
I'll let you have him then.
Ta sẽ đưa bé cho ngươi vậy.
Sure.
Chắn chắn rồi.
The little goat has a mark. You must have one too.
Cừu con có vết bớt. Hẳn ngươi cũng có.
There it is.
Đây rồi.
Is the baby okay?
Bé con ổn chứ?
I haven't examined him yet.
Ta chưa khám xong.
Oh.
Ừ.
I'm not used to having someone looking when I'm examining people.
Ta không quen có người nhìn khi ta khám.
It's okay, I'm not looking at you.
Ta không nhìn ngươi.
I'm looking at the baby.
Ta nhìn bé con.
But you will distract me.
Nhưng ông gây sao nhãng tôi.
I'll leave then.
Ta sẽ đi vậy.
Is the baby okay?
Bé con ổn chứ?
He's okay.
Ổn mà.
If he's okay, I'll take him then.
Nếu ổn, ta sẽ dẫn bé đi.
No. He's not okay.
Không. Không ổn.
What did you say?
Ngươi nói gì?
I'm sorry.
Ta xin lỗi.
When I get anxious, my superpower gets out of control.
Khi lo lắng, ta không kiểm soát được sức mạnh.
What's wrong with the baby?
Bé con bị làm sao?
I mean, he needs some rest.
Ý ta là bé con cần nghỉ ngơi.
Stop holding him everywhere you go.
Đừng bế bé đi khắp nơi.
What should I do with my hair?
Ta nên làm gì với tóc mình?
Let me help you. Shorter hair!
Ta giúp ngươi. Tóc ngắn!
My hair!
Tóc của ta!
Why do you guys keep coming over?
Sao các ngươi cứ tới đây?
I was afraid the baby might be bored when he wakes up.
Ta lo bé con sẽ chán khi dậy.
I'll be there when he wakes up. Just go and have fun.
Ta sẽ ở đây khi bé dậy. Đi chơi đi.
All right.
Được rồi.
Let me help you!
Để ông giúp!
Sorry. My aura is just too strong.
Xin lỗi. Khí chất của ta quá mạnh.
The photo is dirty now.
Bức ảnh bẩn rồi.
I'm sorry.
Ta xin lỗi.
If I hadn't asked Handsome Star to go to Wolffy's senior activity center,
Nếu ta không bảo Sao Đẹp Trai tới viện dưỡng lão của Sói Xám,
the photo wouldn't have flown away and it wouldn't have gotten dirty.
thì bức ảnh đã không bay và bị bẩn mất.
Wolffy has a senior activity center?
Sói Xám có viện dưỡng lão?
Yes. Elder Star and the baby are there now.
Sao Cao Tuổi và bé con đang ở đấy.
You old goat.
Tên cừu già.
Stop struggling.
Đừng vùng vẫy nữa.
Ah!
A!
Don't run!
Đứng lại!
The baby won!
Bé con thắng rồi!
Help!
Cứu!
The baby is amazing.
Bé con thật tuyệt.
Seeing you play makes me want to play badminton too.
Thấy con chơi làm ta muốn chơi cầu lông.
Me too. Baby, be good.
Ta nữa. Bé con hãy ngoan.
Play with Uncle Wolffy.
Chơi với chú Sói Xám.
Yes, give him to me.
Đúng, để bé cho ta.
I won't let you off.
Ta không để ngươi thoát đâu.
Help!
Cứu!
Baby, hush now, or I'll lose.
Bé trật tự không, ta sẽ thua.
Come on, baby. Play with me over here. Don't get in their way.
Bé chơi với ta ở đây. Đừng làm phiền họ.
Yes. This'll make me win.
Ta sắp thắng rồi.
Baby, you're awesome.
Bé con tuyệt vời.
Baby, can you play chess?
Bé có thể chơi cờ?
He can play badminton too.
Bé chơi được cả cầu lông.
That's not all. He got a perfect score bowling.
Bé còn đạt điểm tuyệt đối bowling.
Wow! You're really an invincible baby.
Oa! Bé con là em bé bất bại.
All of you guys underestimate me. Ah!
Các ngươi đánh giá thấp ta. A!
I thought I saw something fly out.
Hình như có gì vừa bay ra.
Chief is all right! That's great.
Trưởng Làng vẫn an toàn!
We just need to clean the photo.
Ta chỉ cần làm sạch bức ảnh.
Chief. We'll find Time Star and get you back to normal.
Trưởng Làng. Ta sẽ tìm Sao Thời Gian và biến ông lại như cũ.
I guess Chief is going to have to drink milk again.
Đến giờ uống sữa của Trưởng Làng rồi.
Baby, we really underestimated you.
Ta đã đánh giá thấp bé con.
You're amazing.
Con thật tuyệt vời.
My heart tells me I want to play chess.
Ta muốn chơi cờ.
Come play with me.
Đến chơi với ta.
Uh, uh.
Vâng.
I'll do anything to avoid drinking milk.
Mình sẽ làm mọi thứ để tránh uống sữa.
But before that, you have to drink your milk.
Nhưng con phải uống sữa đã.